<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.10.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://repository-sxiong.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://repository-sxiong.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2025-08-31T15:30:04+00:00</updated><id>https://repository-sxiong.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Home</title><subtitle>personal description</subtitle><author><name>SONGSONG XIONG</name><email>s.xiong@rug.nl</email></author><entry><title type="html">My Paper Presentation and Session Co-Chair Role at the 34th RO-MAN Conference</title><link href="https://repository-sxiong.github.io/posts/2025/08/roman-presentation-song/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="My Paper Presentation and Session Co-Chair Role at the 34th RO-MAN Conference" /><published>2025-08-26T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-08-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://repository-sxiong.github.io/posts/2025/08/roman-presentation-song</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://repository-sxiong.github.io/posts/2025/08/roman-presentation-song/"><![CDATA[<p>I am excited to share some highlights from my recent academic experience.</p>

<p>My paper, <strong>“LM-MCVT: A Lightweight Multi-modal Multi-view Convolutional-Vision Transformer Approach for 3D Object Recognition”</strong>, was officially accepted at the <strong>34th IEEE International Conference on Robot and Human Interactive Communication (RO-MAN 2025)</strong>, which took place in <strong>Eindhoven, the Netherlands</strong>. During the conference, I delivered a presentation on this work, where I introduced our proposed lightweight framework for 3D object recognition that integrates multi-modal inputs and multi-view representations with a Convolutional-Vision Transformer architecture.</p>

<p>In addition to presenting my research, I was honored to be invited as the <strong>co-chair</strong> of the <strong>“LLM-Enhanced Social Robotics III</strong>. In this role, I led the session discussions and engaged with researchers from around the world who are exploring the role of LLMs in robotics and human-robot interaction. This experience gave me the opportunity to contribute not only as a researcher but also as a session leader, facilitating meaningful academic exchange.</p>

<p>I would like to sincerely thank all the presenters for their outstanding talks and extend my gratitude to the academic community for its continued interest and contributions to multimodal learning and LLM research.</p>

<p>This conference marks an important milestone in my academic journey, reflecting both the progress of my research and my growing involvement in the international robotics and AI community.</p>

<hr />]]></content><author><name>SONGSONG XIONG</name><email>s.xiong@rug.nl</email></author><category term="robotics" /><category term="conference" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am excited to share some highlights from my recent academic experience.]]></summary></entry></feed>